[roars]
[narrator] Strange beasts and monsters.
[squeaking]
Vast riches.
Hidden treasures.
Evil haunts.
Uncharted frontiers.
The mysterious unknown.
The people who are captivated
by the magic in those words...
are called...
Hunters.
[theme music playing]
[Hisoka Morow]
I've decided to let you live, for now.
Until someday, you become
truly worthy of killing.
I will take it back.
But only when you can punch me
in the face like that.
In the meantime, you just hold onto it
for me.
TRAP x IN x THE HOLE
[narrator]
Gon was utterly humiliated after Hisoka
returned the badges
that Geretta had taken.
As for Killua...
[Killua Zoldyck]
You're wasting your time.
Follow me all you want, but
I'll never give you a chance to attack.
[Imori laughs]
Be afraid, kid.
Be very afraid.
I'm a very cautious guy.
I'll do whatever it takes,
even when I'm up against a kid.
Once he's exhausted,
then he has to go to sleep.
I'll strike.
[laughs]
Like I said,
I'm a cautious guy.
[sighs]
Come out or I'll come to you.
[Imori shudders]
This really is a pain, you know.
Chances are,
you're only worth one lousy point.
[Imori]
He wants to fight?
He's just a kid.
I can't lose, right?
But...
Why is he so relaxed?
He can't be that strong, can he?
Right, be cautious.
Because I'm a cautious guy.
Oh, I should escape.
I mean, retreat and reassess.
But...
if I do, my brothers might yell at me.
Wait, what am I saying?
If I go back without his badge,
they're definitely going to yell at me.
[whimpers]
Big brother!
Huh?
We ran into a little trouble.
You must be done by now, right?
[all]
Huh?
Uh....
-What are you, an idiot?
-[Imori yells]
You can't even beat a little kid?
Give me a break.
Hold on, you've got it all wrong,
big brother.
What part do I have wrong?
I-- I didn't want to hurt
a little kid, that's all.
I thought I'd just hold off
and take it while he slept.
You're so full of it.
[Imori]
Fine, you got me.
And you're right.
I guess I should wrap this up.
Time for a beat-down.
[Imori]
At least if I start to lose,
I've got my brothers here to step in
and back me up.
All right, kid.
How about you hand it over?
Do as I say, and you won't get hurt.
Idiot.
[grunts]
[Imori]
Don't go saying I didn't warn you.
[laughs]
Bam, right in the gut.
[Umori] It must hurt like hell.
-[Killua grunts]
-[Imori gasps]
What the hell, bro?
You go easy on this squirt?
Yeah, you're way too nice, Imori.
Oh... Uh, right.
You're number 198, huh?
[whimpers]
No way.
[gasps]
Since it's only a number off
from the one I've been looking for,
I'm betting...
that 199 must be one of you two,
am I right?
[Imori] Uh...
Hey, Umori.
Yeah.
-Get into formation. Let's do this.
-[gasps]
[Amori]
I'm pretty sure he ain't no ordinary kid.
[Imori panting]
[chuckles]
[grunts]
[Amori]
I don't give a damn how strong he is,
he doesn't stand a chance
against our group attack,
nobody does.
[Umori] The three of us have beaten
a lot tougher opponents than him
with this formation.
[Imori]
Just you wait, you brat.
We're gonna tear you to shreds.
Uh... Up there.
[grunts]
-[gasps]
-Don't move, okay?
My fingers here cut a lot better
than any knife.
[Amori whimpers]
[Killua sighs] Aw, man....
You're number 197.
Damn, I really am bad
at guessing these things.
-Hey!
-Huh?
Are you 199?
Yeah.
[Killua]
Give it.
[grumbles]
-[grunts]
-Thank you.
Now then,
for the ones I don't need.
[grumbles]
Humph.
Oh...
And this one goes this way.
-[gasping]
-[Umori grunts]
Good luck.
You've got three days left to find them.
I'll see you later.
[gasp]
[grunts] Damn.
[sighs]
[grunts]
Hm, number 197 was always with 199.
They were basically inseparable.
One thing's for sure, I never expected
that little kid to deal with him for me.
It's a good thing I was watching
from the shadows.
Made it really easy to grab the badge
I nee-- [grunts]
[groans]
He... He knew.
The kid knew I was there!
[grumbles]
I failed.
Oh man, this is so boring.
I wonder what Gon is up to right now.
HUNTER GLOSSARY
Hmm?
TOO BAD
Humph!
[birds singing]
[grunts]
We've been here for six days.
Only one day left.
[Kurapika] It's been four days
since we ran into Hisoka.
And we haven't found anyone else.
[Leorio Paradinight] Hmm.
Maybe we should
go back to the landing.
[Kurapika] Huh?
[Leorio] It's possible there are
a few people who've already finished.
-[Kurapika] No, impossible.
-[Leorio] Huh?
This phase of the Exam is different
from all the others.
If your badge is stolen, you still have
the opportunity to recover it.
On the other hand,
just because you have six points worth
of badges now
doesn't guarantee you'll have them
when the phase ends.
This test can't be completed early.
I see.
[Kurapika]
But it's worth a shot.
With just a day left,
there must be a few
who've already gotten their six points.
And it's safe to assume they would
then gravitate to the same place.
Near the goal.
At least, that's what I would do.
Oh.
Okay, let's get going.
[Leorio]
Well? See anyone?
[Kurapika]
No.
That is to say,
no one who can be easily spotted.
[Leorio]
Damn it.
[Kurapika] Perhaps we should split up
and keep looking.
But first, we should choose
a time and place for us to reconvene.
[Gon] And it will go way faster
with three people.
[Kurapika and Leorio]
Huh?
[both]
Gon.
I guess we all must have had
exactly the same idea.
I've been watching from above
and it looks like there are
a lot of people nearby.
Really? From above?
Now why didn't we think of that?
It wouldn't have worked.
Without eyes as sharp as Gon's,
we'd have never spotted anyone.
-[Kurapika] Gon.
-Huh?
Were you able to get
all the badges you need?
[sighs]
[Gon]
Yeah, I guess.
-Oh, damn. You got yours, too?
-[Kurapika gasps]
So I'm the only one left.
[Gon]
Well, who's your target?
Number 246, a woman named Ponzu.
The only thing I really know about her
is that she uses chemical weapons.
[Leorio]
Gon.
You didn't happen to see any women
when you were up there, did you?
I'm afraid not.
I see.
All right. There are four possibilities
we should consider.
She's safe and still in possession
of her badge.
-She's alive but no longer has her badge.
-[crying]
She's out of the competition
but has held onto her badge.
Or she's dead now,
and doesn't have her badge.
[Leorio]
Do you really think
it's likely that she's both out
of the running and still has her badge?
She might have gotten
in some kind of accident.
Or it's possible that she was defeated
after hiding her badge somewhere
for safe keeping.
If that's the case and she was killed
after concealing her badge,
her badge may never be found again.
The more you talk,
the worse this scenario gets.
Hey, do you know anything else
about Ponzu?
Like, does she wear some kind
of special fragrance, like Leorio?
-[Leorio] Huh?
-[Kurapika gasps] That's right.
Gon might be able to track her
by her scent.
Okay, but she might not even wear perfume,
you know, what do we do then?
-[Kurapika] He'll track her chemicals.
-Huh...
She's well known for using chemicals,
isn't she?
With a variety of chemicals,
some are sure to have distinct odors.
-Well, Gon?
-Right.
I'll give it a shot.
After all, it's why I'm here.
Huh?
[Leorio]
Is she in there, Gon?
[Gon]
Yep, no doubt about it.
What's your plan?
[Leorio]
I'm going in.
I want you guys to wait here.
[rattling echoes]
[Leorio]
Doesn't look like there are any traps.
I'll head inside.
Wait until I get the okay.
Then you two can come in.
-[Kurapika] Thirty minutes.
-Hmm?
If after 30 minutes,
we haven't heard from you,
-we're coming to find you.
-Humph!
-[Leorio] No way.
-[both gasp]
If you don't hear from me,
you both go right back to the start.
-[Kurapika] That's not an option.
-Huh?
We have formed an alliance
and I will not abandon you now.
[sighs]
Then this alliance is over.
I know it's selfish,
considering how much you helped me.
But I've got to do this alone.
-No way.
-[Leorio] Huh?
[yelling]
What did you say?
We're both staying here
because we want to.
[gasps]
It's our choice, so is that a problem?
[grumbles]
[sighs] Fine, suit yourself.
[gasps]
Hang onto that for me.
[sigh]
[both chuckle]
[exhales]
[footsteps approaching]
[grunts, chuckles]
[Leorio]
I've just gotta go for it.
[footsteps echoing]
[breathes heavily]
Hey isn't that... It's Bourbon.
-[woman] Let me guess.
-[gasps]
I must be your target, am I right?
Ponzu!
-[Ponzu] It's pointless.
-Huh?
There's nothing for us to gain
by fighting down here.
I have everything to gain.
It's just like you said,
you're my target, all right!
This is happening, no matter what.
[sighs]
Let's assume that we do fight and
by some miracle, you actually beat me.
There's still no way
you're ever getting out of this cave.
Wait, what?
What are you talking about?
[chirping]
[Gon]
He's taking too long.
So what do you think,
is he okay?
Yes.
But his 30 minutes are almost up.
[Leorio, shouting]
Kurapika, Gon!
-Don't come in!
-[both gasp]
[Gon]
Leorio!
[gasp]
[grunts]
Huh?
[Gon]
Leorio!
You idiots.
I thought I told you
not to come in.
[Kurapika]
He's covered in bites.
If those snakes are venomous, then...
They're a kind of viper.
And they are poisonous,
but it isn't that strong.
Still, with this many bites...
[Leorio groaning]
Stop it, will you?
One cut in your mouth,
or even a little cavity...
Don't worry about it.
[Kurapika] Leorio,
do you have any anti-venom in here?
If I did...
maybe...
I would have been able...
to save you guys, at least.
[sighs]
Leorio!
Let's stop the bleeding.
[breathing heavily]
That should do it.
We still need to get him to a doctor.
-[Ponzu] I wouldn't advise that.
-[Gon and Kurapika gasp]
You aren't getting out so easily.
What do you mean by that?
[Ponzu]
What I mean is that we're trapped.
Whenever someone tries
to leave this cave...
[hissing]
...the snakes will attack you en masse.
[gasp]
[loud hissing]
It's a trap set by Bourbon,
the snake charmer.
If you're bitten,
you'll end up completely paralyzed,
just like your friend here.
After that, you die.
[Kurapika] Bourbon, you're looking
to collect more badges, right?
We'll give you every one we have.
Just please, let us out of here.
Don't bother.
[Ponzu]
You see, he's already dead.
[Kurapika]
What? You can't be serious.
[narrator] Gon and friends
are caught in a trap set by Bourbon,
the snake charmer,
and can't leave the cave.
Will they pass the Hunter Exam?
And will Leorio survive
the venomous snake bites?
[hissing]
[grunts]
[theme song playing]
[Gon] Next time,
"Big x Time x Interview."
Thanks a lot, Kurapika.
[Kurapika]
No, thank you, Gon.